[Music]
so
and to start a conversation in Chinese
so last year in 2017 the visits the
challenge beyond impose on ourselves how
do we change the market unfortunately
even if we are very happy for the answer
the highest in service for the best and
finest speakers everything capacitors
people talk about insurance traditional
traditional and insurance OTT big event
and then so insurance really emotional
nice play Charlie
and what we need you wanted to fool
let's change one of my tweets because
people talk about insurance or pay
attention on that speech pathologist or
finance everything different and your
emotions hold love and support and and
make our country and the other thing we
consider every was that probably the
tear in his or through the dates are not
going to spend much time on very much
and even as we manage to gather each
other words so we also want them to
change the little bit of a message right
in through this me with edu and crazy
old Brittany of us and when we work our
London out there we ask ourselves what
we wanted to see and you to prefer 100th
anniversary rather than we perspective
he realizes power around business and
evidence-based and that's that was only
designed it so our videos and other
particulates this is regarding
[Applause]
[Music]
in an industry where one might even be
with us through the actual physics
percent version so what relatable
content in that veneer in a matter that
could be in this game is humorous
actually generates not engage the
convert into sales
so whenever we paint it for a second
level you got nowhere to react to each
other than last night when we think it
works so well again because it was
different you want to live to stand out
and stand off so now it was solution for
us become very very calculated this one
shouldn't feed my wallets of Millennials
will be supported us it's also very
believable it's distorting if any of us
can they need to be versus your most
employment me for us to allow us to
deliver a message about time you let me
say that we are here early even people
screams earlier difficult life not just
connect with whom I kept developing
people's thanks that hurts but with that
thank you and I was really
[Applause]
what does implicate the refuted your
sales and marketing having word from
Paris to see fast-moving consumer goods
consumer knowledge the C name is equated
event